Register of the Institute of Economic Affairs (Great Britain) records
Hoover Institution Archives
- 2014 Incremental Materials, 1940-2005
  - Conference evaluation form summary, 2005 (Box-folder 488: 10)
  - IEA financial documents, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 488: 11)
  - Trustees meeting, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 488: 12-14)
  - Correspondence regarding trustees meeting, 2005 (Box-folder 489: 1)
  - Planning materials regarding June reception, 2005 (Box-folder 489: 2)
  - Correspondence, 2005 (Box-folder 489: 3)
  - Shipping reciepts, 2005 (Box-folder 489: 4)
  - Miscellaneous materials, 2005 (Box-folder 489: 5)
  - "Streamlining Governments" from the Pioneer Institute, 2005 (Box-folder 489: 6)
  - Correspondence, 01/2005-12/2005 (Box-folder 489: 7-9)
  - Lord Harris travel, 2005 (Box-folder 489: 10)
  - Correspondence, 11/2004 (Box-folder 489: 11)
  - IEA Future events, 2004 (Box-folder 489: 12)
  - Job Applications, 2004 (Box-folder 489: 13)
  - Job applications, 1996 (Box-folder 490: 1)
  - Conference flyers, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 490: 2)
  - Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 490: 3)
  - IEA staff/visitor list, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 490: 4-6)
  - John Blundell writings and correspondence, 2004 (Box-folder 490: 7)
  - Correspondence, 03/2004-05/2004 (Box-folder 490: 8-9)
  - Notes de l'Institute Thomas More, 2004 (Box-folder 490: 10)
  - Correspondence, 02/2004-03/2004 (Box-folder 490: 11)
  - Harry Walker Agency Inc, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 490: 12)
  - Correspondence, 07/2004-08/2004 (Box-folder 490: 13)
  - Correspondence, 11/2004-1/2005 (Box-folder 491: 1-2)
  - Trustees meeting, 05/2004 (Box-folder 491: 3-4)
  - Job Applications, 2001 (Box-folder 491: 5)
  - Trustees meeting, 2002-2004 (Box-folder 491: 6-8)
  - Correspondence, 01/2004-02/2004 (Box-folder 491: 9-11)
  - Miscellaneous materials, 03/2004-06/2004 (Box-folder 492: 1)
  - Correspondence, 2004 (Box-folder 492: 2)
  - Correspondence, notes, and business cards, 2004 (Box-folder 492: 3)
  - Correspondence, 9/2003-12/2004 (Box-folder 492: 4-9)
    Contains floppy disk.
  - George Walker, 2004 (Box-folder 492: 10)
  - Trustees meeting, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 493: 1-8)
  - John Blundell Director General, 2003 (Box-folder 493: 9)
  - correspondence, 2003 (Box-folder 493: 10-11)
  - Correspondence, 03/2003-05/2003 (Box-folder 494: 1)
  - Trustees meeting, 06/2003 (Box-folder 494: 2)
  - Correspondence, 11/2002-05/2003 (Box-folder 494: 3-5)
  - Trustees meeting, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 494: 6-7)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (Box-folder 494: 8)
  - Trustees meeting, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 494: 9-12)
  - Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 495: 1-4)
  - IEA Article Listing, 2001 (Box-folder 495: 5)
  - Barbara Shenfield Papers, 1940-1997
    Printed matter, correspondence, and clippings.
    - Nationalisation: a Report by the Federation of British Industries, 1958 (Box-folder 495: 6)
    - The Man Versus the State by Herbert Spencer, 1940 (Box-folder 495: 7)
    - Capitalism and the Historians by Freidrich A. Hayek, 1960 (Box-folder 495: 8)
    - Prices and Production by Friedrich A. Hayek, 1967 (Box-folder 495: 9)
    - Management and Machiavelli by Antony Jay, 1967 (Box-folder 495: 10)
    - "F.A. Hayek Essay Competition: Winning Essays,", 1996 (Box-folder 495: 11)
    - "The Facts of Hayek" by Frank Johnson, undated (Box-folder 496: 1)
    - Correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 496: 2)
    - Photographs, undated (Box-folder 496: 3)
    - Mont Pelerin Society Newsletter, 1980-1997 (Box-folder 496: 4-5)
    - Mont Pelerin Society essays, undated (Box-folder 496: 6)
    - Articles by Milton Friedman, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 496: 7)
    - Mont Pelerin Society essays, 1972-1997 (Box-folder 496: 8)
  - Mont Pelerin Society essays, 1965-1980 (Box-folder 496: 9)
  - Scholarly essays, 1998 (Box-folder 496: 10)
  - Mont Pelerin Society General Meeting London, 2002 (Box-folder 496: 11)
  - Journal of the IEA Volume 22, Number 1, 2002 (Box-folder 496: 12)
  - Mont Pelerin Society General Meeting London, 2002 (Box-folder 497: 1)
  - Antony Fisher Champion of Liberty by Gerald Frost, 2002 (Box-folder 497: 2)
  - "A History of the Sir Antony Fisher International Memorial Awards,", 2002 (Box-folder 497: 3)
  - Poleconomy boardgame, circa 1990s-2000s (Boxes 498-499)